// HTML & CSS
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is -",
    answer: "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
    options: [
      "Head, Title, HTML, body",
      "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
      "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
      "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A Much Better Approach To Establish The Base URL Is To Use The ______ Element",
    answer: "BASE",
    options: [
      "BODY",
      "BASE",
      "HEAD",
      "None Of The Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is -",
    answer: "background-color",
    options: [
      "bgcolor",
      "color",
      "background-color",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is -",
    answer: "style",
    options: [
      "style",
      "styles",
      "class",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to make the background-color of all paragraph elements to yellow?",
    answer: "p {background-color : yellow;}",
    options: [
      "p {background-color : yellow;}",
      "p {background-color : #yellow;}",
      "all {background-color : yellow;}",
      "all p {background-color : #yellow;}"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The CSS property used to make the text bold is -",
    answer: "font-weight : bold",
    options: [
      "weight: bold",
      "font-weight : bold",
      "font: bold",
      "style: bold"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is -",
    answer: "opacity",
    options: [
      "filter",
      "visibility",
      "overlay",
      "opacity"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What are the types of lists available in HTML?",
    answer: "Ordered, Unordered Lists.",
    options: [
      "Named, Unnamed Lists.",
      "Bulleted, Numbered Lists.",
      "Ordered, Unordered Lists.",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the father of HTML?",
    answer: "Tim Berners-Lee",
    options: [
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Tim Berners-Lee",
      "Brendan Eich",
      "Sergey Brin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following CSS property is used to specify the space between every letter inside an element?",
    answer: "letter-spacing",
    options: [
      "alpha-spacing",
      "character-spacing",
      "letter-spacing",
      "alphabet-spacing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The CSS property used to specify whether the text is written in the horizontal or vertical direction?",
    answer: "writing-mode",
    options: [
      "writing-mode",
      "text-indent",
      "word-break",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which of the following is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
    answer: "Web browser",
    options: [
      "Web server",
      "Web network",
      "Web matrix",
      "Web browser"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What is DOM in HTML?",
    answer: "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents",
    options: [
      "Application programming interface",
      "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents",
      "Language dependent application programming",
      "Hierarchy of objects in ASP.NET"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to select the p siblings of a div element?",
    answer: "div ~ p",
    options: [
      "div p",
      "div ~ p",
      "p",
      "div + p"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following is not the element associated with the HTML table layout?",
    answer: "color",
    options: [
      "alignment",
      "color",
      "size",
      "spanning"
    ]
  },
];